Finding Aid for Center for Afroamerican and African Studies (University of Michigan) records, 1966-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Audio recordings on cassettes 1975-2001
  - Brown Bag
    - Tiffany Patterson: The politics of Post-Colonial Studies and the African Diaspora 1994-02-01, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-191-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-191-2
    - Angela D. Dillard: Religion and civil rights mobilizations in Detroit 1935-1967 1994-02-04, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-192-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-192-2
    - Earl Lewis: All because of the color of your skin 1994-02-15, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-193-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-193-2
    - Rei M. Terada: History's innocence or is it remorse? 1994-03-01, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-194-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-194-2
    - Jacqueline Mattis: When and Where they Enter: The Sexual Politics of Psychological Research and Practice 1994-03-04, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-195-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-195-2
    - Nii Quarcoopome: Majestic Rides into the Afterlife: Coffins and Status in an African Community 1994-03-15, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-196-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-196-2
    - Terry Epstein and Cynthia Renfro: Representations of Race in 19th and 20th Century History Textbooks 1994-03-22, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-197-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-197-2
    - Lorna Goodison: Poetry reading 1994-03-23, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-198-1
    - Kyra Gaunt: An Analysis of Hip-Hop Sampling: A Multiplicity of Heterogeneous Sound in Time, Space and Memory 1994-03-29, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-199-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-199-2
    - Lester Monts: Music and Ritual Structures in Pre-Islamic and Present Day Vai (Liberia) Funerary Sequences 1994-04-04, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-200-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-200-2
    - Gina Ulysse: That cunning Jamaican woman: Dem foreign higglers and the state 1995-09-28, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-201-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-201-2
    - Heidi L. Ardizzone: Bodies of evidence: Race, color, and character in the Rhinelander annulment case 1995-10-12, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-202-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-202-2
  - Dialogue
    - John U. Ogbu: Professor UC Berkeley and author of Minority Education and caste: The American system in cross-cultural perspective 1991-10-04, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-203-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-203-2
    - Kenneth J. Knuckles: Commissioner New York City Department of General Services 1991-10-04, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-204-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-204-2
    - Nicholas Lemann: Author of Promised Land: The Great Black Migration and How It Changed America 1991-10-15, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-205-1
    - Benjamin Davis, Veronica Jennings and Ivan Roman: Journalism 1991-10-24, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-207-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-207-2
    - Martin Bernal: Author of Black Athena: The Afro-asiatic Roots of Classical Civilization 1991-11-04, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-208-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-208-2
    - Lawrence Bobo: Co-author of Racial Attitudes in America: Trends and Interpretations 1992-01-21, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-213-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-213-2
    - Ronald Ferguson: Author of Social and Economic Prospects of African American Males: Why Reading, Math, and Social Development Should be Leadership Priorities 1992-02-03, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-214-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-214-2
    - Abena Busia: Poet and author of Testimonies of Exile 1992-02-04, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-215-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-215-2
    - Judge A. Leon Higginbotham: U.S. Court of Appeals and author of In the Matter of Color: Race and the American Legal Process 1992-02-14, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-216-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-216-2
    - Hilbourne A. Watson: Author of The New World Order and the Crisis of Hegemony 1992-03-13, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-217-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-217-2
    - Nataki H. Goodall: TLC, Female Rap and Female Sexuality 1992-10-04, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-218-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-218-2
    - Jamie Hart: Who should have the children? Discussions of Reproduction Among African American Intellectuals from 1920 to 1939 1992-11-19, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-219-1
    - Mohamed Mbodj: National Identity in Gambia 1993-03-19, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-220-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-220-2
    - Stephen Marc: The Black Trans-Atlantic Experience 1993-03-26, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-221-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-221-2
  - Robert Hyaden Memorial
    - Faculty, students and guests: Poetry readings 1990-02-22, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-222-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-222-2
    - Darwin T. Turner: The Achievement of Robert Hayden 1990-02-22, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-223-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-223-2
    - Michael Harper: Poetry reading 1990-02-22, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-224-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-224-2
    - Michael Harper: Poetry reading 1990-02-22, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-225-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-225-2
    - Pontheolia T. Williams, Darwin T. Turner and Laurence Goldstein: Robert Hayden: His Evolution as an Artist 1990-02-23, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-226-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-226-2
    - Eugene Redmond, Xavier Nichols & Richard Tillinghast: Robert Hayden: Blues poet or modernist? 1990-02-23, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-227-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-227-2
    - Michael S. Harper: The Voice and Vision of Robert Hayden 1990-02-23, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-228-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-228-2
    - Gwendolyn Brooks: Poetry reading 1990-02-23, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-229-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-229-2
    - John Hatcher, Melba Boyd, Alan Wald & Lemuel Johnson: The tension between belief and ideology in the work of Robert Hayden 1990-02-24, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-230-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-230-2
    - John Hatcher, Melba Boyd, Alan Wald & Lemuel Johnson: The tension between belief and ideology in the work of Robert Hayden 1990-02-24, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-231-1
    - Sherley Anne Williams: Poetry reading 1990-02-24, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-232-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-232-2
    - John W. Aldridge, Alvin Aubert, Melba Boyd, Gwendolyn Brooks, Michael S. Harper, John Hatcher, Pinkie Gordon Lane, Naomi Long Madgett, Dudley Randall, Eugene Redmond, Ronald Scott: Poems, memories and testimonials 1990-02-24, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-233-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-233-2
    - John W. Aldridge, Alvin Aubert, Melba Boyd, Gwendolyn Brooks, Michael S. Harper, John Hatcher, Pinkie Gordon Lane, Naomi Long Madgett, Dudley Randall, Eugene Redmond, Ronald Scott: Poems, memories and testimonials 1990-02-24, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-234-1
    - Rita Dove: Poetry reading 1990-02-24, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-235-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-235-2
  - Workshop on Strengthening CAAS and Africana Studies at U-M
    - Evelyn Barbee and Lemuel Johnson: Introduction, Q&A 1989-04-25, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-236-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-236-2
    - Walter Allen and Nesha Haniff: Ford Foundation grant / proposal and what it means to the Center's future 1989-04-25, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-237-1
    - Walter Allen and Nesha Haniff: Ford Foundation grant / proposal and what it means to the Center's future 1989-04-25, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-238-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-238-2
    - Administrative issues in seeking departmental issues circa 1989-04-24, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-239-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-239-2
    - Governance with fewer faculty circa 1989-04-24, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-240-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-240-2
    - Long-range goals of CAAS circa 1989-04-24, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-241-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-241-2
    - Role of the CAAS library circa 1989-04-24, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-242-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-242-2
    - Role of the CAAS library circa 1989-04-24, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-243-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-243-2
  - CAAS Symposium for Black History Month: Black American Families
    - Fred McCuiston, Larry Fox, William Ratcliff and Michael Cross: Young, Black, and Male in America: An Endangered Species 1991-02-14, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-244-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-244-2
    - Fred McCuiston, Larry Fox, William Ratcliff and Michael Cross: Young, Black, and Male in America: An Endangered Species 1991-02-14, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-245-1
    - Earl Lewis, DeWitt S. Dykes, Jr. and Robert J. Taylor: Black Families: A Status Report 1991-02-15, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-246-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-246-2
    - Vonnie C. McLoyd, Susan Frazier-Kouassi and Philip Bowman: Mothers, Fathers, Grandparents 1991-02-15, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-247-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-247-2
    - Andrea G. Hunter, Oscar Barbarin III and Toni C. Antonucci: Hunter: Mothers, Fathers, Grandparents; Barbarin & Antonucci: Families Coping with Stress 1991-02-15, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-248-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-248-2
    - James S. Jackson: Families Coping with Stress 1991-02-15, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-249-1
    - Vycki Johnson: Workshop: Black Youths 1991-02-16, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-250-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-250-2
    - Andrea G. Hunter and Henry Davis: Workshop: Afro-American Men's Views of Male Family Roles 1991-02-16, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-251-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-251-2
    - Susan Frazier-Kouassi: Workshop: Black, Single Parent Women: Future Directions 1991-02-16, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-252-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-252-2
    - DeWitt S. Dykes, Jr.: Workshop: Methods for tracing Black Family Genealogy 1991-02-16, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-253-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-253-2
  - Inventions of Africa: Africa in the Literatures of the Continent and the Diaspora Workshops
    - Maxwell Owusu, E. Nii Quarcoopome and Lorna McDaniel: Workshop 1: African Voices: Literature in Context 1991-10-23, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-254-1
    - Maxwell Owusu, E. Nii Quarcoopome and Lorna McDaniel: Workshop 1: African Voices: Literature in Context 1991-10-23, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-255-1
    - Abena Busia: Workshop 3: The Construction of the Absence of Black Women in the Discourse 1992-02-04, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-257-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-257-2
  - CAAS 20th Anniversary
    - Charles D. Moody: Opening Remarks 1991-03-15, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-259-1
    - Keynote address: Establishing New Paradigms: The Creation & Growth of Africana Studies 1991-03-15, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-260-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-260-2
    - Panel: From BAM to CAAS "Origins and Aims of CAAS" 1991-03-15, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-261-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-261-2
    - Panel: From BAM to CAAS "Origins and Aims of CAAS" 1991-03-15, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-262-1
    - Panel: Models for African Studies 1991-03-15, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-263-1
    - Panel: Models for African Studies 1991-03-15, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-264-1
    - Panel: New Curriculum Options 1991-03-15, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-265-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-265-2
    - Awards 1991-03-15, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-266-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-266-2
    - Emery Smith, Roderick Linzie, Stephanie Johnson, Devlin Ponte and Abdul Goler: Workshop: The Next Generation of Scholars: Towards a Student-centered Academy 1991-03-16, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-267-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-267-2
    - Emery Smith, Roderick Linzie, Stephanie Johnson, Devlin Ponte and Abdul Goler: Workshop: The Next Generation of Scholars: Towards a Student-centered Academy 1991-03-16, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-268-1
    - Tracye Matthews, Brenda Flanagan, Jan Collins-Eaglin and Linda Chatters: Workshop: The Dynamics of Gender in Africana Studies and the Academy 1991-03-16, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-269-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-269-2
    - Tracye Matthews, Brenda Flanagan, Jan Collins-Eaglin and Linda Chatters: Workshop: The Dynamics of Gender in Africana Studies and the Academy 1991-03-16, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-270-1
    - J. Frank Yates: Closing: Challenges for Future Development 1991-03-16, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-271-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-271-2
  - Race, Culture and the Politics of Intellectual Inquiry Lecture Series
    - Patricia Williams: Equality's Demise and the Problem of Black Identity 1991-11-04, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-272-1
    - Manning Marable: Of Our Spiritual Strivings: Black America Searches for Itself 1992-01-10, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-274-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-274-2
    - Evelyn Brooks Higginbotham: Race, History and Feminist Theory 1992-02-14, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-275-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-275-2
    - George Lipsitz: As Nasty as They Wanna Be: Racial Politics and Intellectual Inquiry 1991-03-13, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-276-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-276-2
    - K. Anthony Appiah: Ancestral Voices: The Case for an African American Philosophy 1992-04-03, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-277-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-277-2
    - K. Anthony Appiah: Ancestral Voices: The Case for an African American Philosophy 1992-04-03, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-278-1
  - Remapping of Scholarship: African peoples in the Industrial Age
    - Michael Awkward, Earl Lewis, John Higginson, Tyler Stovall, Joe Trotter: Opening 1994-09-30, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-279-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-279-2
    - Joe Trotter, Keletso Atkins and Tiffany Patterson: Panel 1 1994-09-30, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-280-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-280-2
    - Open discussion: Open discussion 1994-09-30, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-281-1
    - Nahun Chandler, Antonio Sergio, Alfredo Guimaraes and Denise Hood: Panel 2: Social and Political Identities 1994-10-01, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-282-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-282-2
    - Hanes Walton, B. Nantang Jua: Comments 1994-10-01, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-283-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-283-2
    - Carolyn Cooper, Abiola Irele 1994-10-01, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-284-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-284-2
  - Graduate Student Conference [became Student of Color of Rackham (SCOR]
    - Dean John D'Arms, Todd Shaw, Cheedy Jaja, Bilinda Straight, Lemuel Johnson: Session 1: Frameworks for Afro-American and African Studies 1991-02-01, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-285-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-285-2
    - Dean John D'Arms, Todd Shaw, Cheedy Jaja, Bilinda Straight, Lemuel Johnson: Session 1: Frameworks for Afro-American and African Studies 1991-02-01, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-286-1
    - Otto Gonzalez, John Stiles, Gracia Clark & Keletso Atkins: Session 2A: To Be a Colonial: Life in a Colonial and Post-Colonial World 1991-02-02, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-292-1
    - Otto Gonzalez, John Stiles, Gracia Clark & Keletso Atkins: Session 2A: To Be a Colonial: Life in a Colonial and Post-Colonial World 1991-02-02, audiocassette (Box 32)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-293-1
    - Raynal Harris, Eric Porter, Valerie Sweeney Prince, Nancy Cho & Jimmie L. Reeves: Session 1: Negotiations of Culture: Aesthetic, Spatial and Textual 1993-02-04, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-294-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-294-2
    - Raynal Harris, Eric Porter, Valerie Sweeney Prince, Nancy Cho & Jimmie L. Reeves: Session 1: Negotiations of Culture: Aesthetic, Spatial and Textual 1993-02-04, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-295-1
    - Gina Barclay-McLaughlin, Petula Brown, Pamela Joshi, Lynetta Mosby, Shilpa Dave & Donald R. Deskins, Jr.: Session 2: Racial Equity and Public Policy 1993-02-04, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-296-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-296-2
    - Gina Barclay-McLaughlin, Petula Brown, Pamela Joshi, Lynetta Mosby, Shilpa Dave & Donald R. Deskins, Jr.: Session 2: Racial Equity and Public Policy 1993-02-04, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-297-1
    - Laurent Dubois, Jean M. Leverich, Beth Notar, Natalie Bennett & Simon Gikandi: Session 3: Race and National Identity: Beyond the United States 1993-02-04, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-298-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-298-2
    - Laurent Dubois, Jean M. Leverich, Beth Notar, Natalie Bennett & Simon Gikandi: Session 3: Race and National Identity: Beyond the United States 1993-02-04, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-299-1
    - Michele Tracy Berger, Susan Edwards and Susan Jenkins: Session 4: "I See, Therefore You Are?" The Body, the Gaze and the Self 1993-02-04, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-300-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-300-2
    - Michele Tracy Berger, Susan Edwards and Susan Jenkins: Session 4: "I See, Therefore You Are?" The Body, the Gaze and the Self 1993-02-04, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-301-1
    - Natasha Barnes, Bill Tivenan and Valerie Nao Yoshimura: Session 5: "Things ain't change, they just rearrange": Gender and racial metamorphoses 1993-02-04, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-302-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-302-2
    - Natasha Barnes, Bill Tivenan and Valerie Nao Yoshimura: Session 5: "Things ain't change, they just rearrange": Gender and racial metamorphoses 1993-02-04, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-303-1
    - Ana M. Biaz, Joseph Dorsey, Nancy Hopkins Donnell Walton, Max Weintraub, Rama Sethi and Dorceta Taylor: Session 6: Activism and agitation: The role of science and economics in social change 1993-02-04, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-304-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-304-2
    - Ana M. Biaz, Joseph Dorsey, Nancy Hopkins Donnell Walton, Max Weintraub, Rama Sethi and Dorceta Taylor: Session 6: Activism and agitation: The role of science and economics in social change 1993-02-04, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-305-1
    - Lynn Perry, Erika Hayes, Jocelyn Finley-Nickelson, Stacy Blake, Yvonne "Baubie" Paschal and Alfred L. Edwards: Session 7: Workforce 2000: Managing beyond black and white in corporate America 1993-02-04, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-306-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-306-2
    - Lynn Perry, Erika Hayes, Jocelyn Finley-Nickelson, Stacy Blake, Yvonne "Baubie" Paschal and Alfred L. Edwards: Session 7: Workforce 2000: Managing beyond black and white in corporate America 1993-02-04, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-307-1
    - Heidi Ardizzone, Miriam Duchess Harris, Grace yoon-aie Pang, Frances Rivera and Earl Lewis: Session 8: Race and National Identity: Considerations of America(ness) 1993-02-04, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-308-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-308-2
    - Heidi Ardizzone, Miriam Duchess Harris, Grace yoon-aie Pang, Frances Rivera and Earl Lewis: Session 8: Race and National Identity: Considerations of America(ness) 1993-02-04, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-309-1
  - Barbados
    - Stanley Greaves 1989-05-15, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-310-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-310-2
    - Jocelyn Massiah 1989-05-15, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-311-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-311-2
    - George Lamming 2012-05-16, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-312-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-312-2
    - George Lamming 2012-05-16, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-313-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-313-2
    - Aggrey Brown 1989-05-17, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-314-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-314-2
    - Aggrey Brown 1989-05-17, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-315-1
    - Ricky Singh 1989-05-17, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-316-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-316-2
    - Ricky Singh 1989-05-17, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-317-1
    - Kathleen Drayton 1989-05-18, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-318-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-318-2
    - Kathleen Drayton 1989-05-18, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-319-1
    - Hilary Beckles 1989-05-19, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-320-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-320-2
    - Hilary Beckles 1989-05-19, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-321-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-321-2
    - Dorbrene O'Marde 1989-05-22, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-323-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-323-2
    - Dorbrene O'Marde 1989-05-22, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-324-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-324-2
    - Roderick Rainford and Peggy Antrobus 1989-05-22, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-325-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-325-2
    - Peggy Antrobus 1989-05-22, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-326-1
    - Peggy Antrobus 1989-05-22, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-327-1
    - Vanda Radzig 1989-05-22, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-328-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-328-2
    - Vanda Radzig 1989-05-22, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-329-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-329-2
    - Lemuel Johnson 1989-05-24, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-330-1
  - Martin Luther King Day
    - Bennet: Tribute to Dr. Martin Luther King 1987-01-17, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-331-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-331-2